<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Data>
  <Add Id="5547566e-69ce-4199-8fed-0b9df653d704" Keywords="Salmon, salad" Image="MediaArchive:d5c85c06-13b8-4af4-bf40-0dc4685fa801" Title="Salmon &amp; Zucchini Vol-Au-Vent With Alfredo Sauce On Bean &amp; Almond Salad" UrlTitle="Salmon-Zucchini-Vol-Au-Vent-With-Alfredo-Sauce-On-Bean--Almond-Salad" MealType="bdaeef60-e1c0-41ab-8baa-99b1cc2d9d0c" Description="&lt;html xmlns=&quot;http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml&quot;&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;head /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;  &lt;body /&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;" Instructions="&lt;html xmlns=&quot;http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml&quot;&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a large non-stick skillet, heat half the oil.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cook zucchini and celery for 2 to 3 minutes. Season and set aside on a plate.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In the same skillet, heat remaining oil. Place salmon cubes and cook for 2 minutes on each side. Season.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add Alfredo sauce and cook for 1 to 2 minutes. Remove from heat. Add reserved vegetables. Mix gently.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cook beans for 1 minute in a pot of boiling water. Strain and set aside.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a skillet, brown almonds for a few minutes. Set aside.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a bowl, combine blanched beans, toasted almonds and remaining salad ingredients. Season.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Serve on a plate. Place salad on the bottom with a vol-au-vent on top. Add creamy sauce to salmon.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Chef's secret&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Don’t overcook the salmon. It will finish cooking in the Alfredo sauce and stay nice and juicy.&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;br /&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;" Difficulty="372b18ed-06fd-49c2-9a7f-90a3465db26d" Date="2022-03-07 16:39:05Z" DietType="" CuisineType="9ca94c8b-33d9-4e8c-9ef7-76772f559f9f" PreparationTime="10" CookingTime="9" Servings="4" PageId="c9344cca-14e3-4430-95de-ea5949f62e10" PublicationStatus="published" SourceCultureName="en-CA" />
  <Add Id="aa2f11ea-5fe5-44dc-b5b6-29a9717b467f" Keywords="Pizza, dinner" Image="MediaArchive:ff7debb9-d9a5-454a-99d0-ac7b41cb1441" Title="Margherita Pizza by Stefano Faita" UrlTitle="Margherita-Pizza-by-Stefano-Faita" MealType="165bc213-8d25-40bb-aca7-2044e333ce63" Description="&lt;html xmlns=&quot;http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml&quot;&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;Crispy oven baked Pizza proposed by the chef Stefano Faita&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;" Instructions="&lt;html xmlns=&quot;http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml&quot;&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;head&gt;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In a large bowl, combine flours and salt.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In another smaller bowl, combine water, yeast and 1 tsp of extra-virgin olive oil.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Add the liquid mix to the dry mix.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knead the mix by hand, about 3 minutes, ensuring all ingredients are well incorporated. Let rest at room temperature for 15 minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Knead again for 3 minutes. Divide dough into 2 equal parts and shape into balls.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Place the dough on a well-floured work surface, cover with damp cloth and let rise at room temperature for 3-4 hours. (You may also refrigerate the dough from 8 to 24 hours. When ready to use, the dough must come to room temperature for 30-45 minutes before use).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Preheat oven at 500°F.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Place a pizza stone on the middle oven rack and heat for at least 1 hour.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Place each ball on a well-floured workspace and, using fingers, stretch out the dough in all directions at first. Then shape into circle or square, as desired.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Put the sauce in the middle of the stretched-out dough and, using the back of a spoon, spread it on the surface, leaving a ½ inch border for the crust.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drizzle with olive oil. Break up mozzarella in big chunks and place them on the sauce. Add basil leaf pieces.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Using a pizza peel, slide one pizza on the stone in the oven. Bake 4 to 8 minutes, or until crust is golden brown and the cheese is bubbling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#x9;&lt;/body&gt;&#xA;&lt;/html&gt;" Difficulty="44de15e3-4fd9-4f61-be66-23f0521c4ebb" Date="2022-03-07 16:34:37Z" DishType="96ee8462-0d86-4e35-b41b-b47251a4a01e" DietType="21521d19-df6c-4823-988b-07c134dce1e4" CuisineType="9ca94c8b-33d9-4e8c-9ef7-76772f559f9f" PreparationTime="15" CookingTime="8" Servings="2" PageId="c9344cca-14e3-4430-95de-ea5949f62e10" PublicationStatus="published" SourceCultureName="en-CA" />
</Data>